(Leonard:)What happened?
(Penny:)Well, I went over to Mike's
to make up with him...
Yeah, no, I know that part.
(Penny:)But he had already moved on.
Already? That was quick.
(Penny:)That's what I said to the woman
who had her legs wrapped around his neck.
(Leonard:)Oh, Penny, I am so sorry.
How could he do that?
Oh, you know,
you did throw an 80-gig iPod...
Yeah, no, how could he do that?
(Penny:)I swear to God,
I am done with guys like that.
(Penny:)You know, macho with the perfect body,
and the hair and the money.
(Leonard:)Yeah, that must get old quick.
(Penny:)You know, just once, I would like to go out
with someone who is nice and honest...
(Penny:)...and who actually cares about me.
[WHIMPERS]
(Leonard:)What about me?
(Penny:)What about you what?
[CRYING]
(Leonard:)What about if you went out with me?